disneyfoodblog.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy | the disney food blog

**Privacy Policy**  
The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Disney Food Blog and how it is used.

Disney Food Blog will not share your personal information with any third party, nor will we sell your personal information with any third party. Ever.

Newsletter  
Any personally identifiable information you provide through the newsletter registration on DisneyFoodBlog.com is used by the site only to send you the Disney Food Blog Newsletter and various Disney Food Blog announcements. You can cancel your newsletter subscriptions at any time.

External Links  
DisneyFoodBlog.com contains external links to other sites that may gather, sell or share personal information. Please see the linked site’s privacy policy for details.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, Disney Food Blog makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies and Web Beacons  
Disney Food Blog may use cookies to store information about visitor preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, customize Web page content based on visitor browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use technology to monitor the advertisements and links that appear on DisneyFoodBlog.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

DisneyFoodBlog.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. DisneyFoodBlog.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

Disney Food Blog is not an official site of The Walt Disney Company or of Universal Studios. Content of DisneyFoodBlog.com is © Cambrick Yard, LLC 2009-2010. Website content may not be reproduced in whole or in part without the prior written permission of DisneyFoodBlog.com.
